It's a recipe for disaster.
The Baker is a comedy, crime, thriller film directed by Gareth Lewis.
Milo is a professional hit man living on the edge.
When failing to fulfill a contract for the first time, he
escapes the city to avoid the wrath of his employers.
Hiding out in a remote rural village, the locals mistake him for the new baker.
Milo, played by Damian Lewis.
Rhiannon, played by Kate Ashfield.
Bjorn, played by Nikolaj Coster-Waldau.
Leo, played by Michael Gambon.
Eggs, played by Dyfan Dwyfor.
Rhys Edwards, played by Anthony O'Donnell.
The Baker is a 2007 British comedy crime thriller film written and directed by Gareth
Lewis and starring Damian Lewis, Kate Ashfield and Nikolaj Coster-Waldau.
An ex-assassin retires to a small Welsh village and opens a
bakery but is unable to escape his former associates.
The film premiered at the 2007 edition of the short-lived Tremblant
Film Festival, where Lewis was awarded Best Director.
After a brief theatrical release, the film was
released to home video as Assassin in Love.
The film explores themes of undercover, hitman, paranoia, black humor, bakery.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.